This video is for you to introduce the relevant update of the chain.
In the previous version, when you need to change the attribute of a more than 3D chain on a piece of clothing,
you must choose one by one and modify each chain.
In the 2025.1 version, the object window added a new chain selection card.
You can manage the chain according to the sample, and store and apply it to the entire chain.
First of all, when you see the object window, a new chain selection is added here.
From the current version, the operation related to the chain will be controlled by this selection card.
Press the increase button in the upper right corner to create a new default chain pattern.
Then apply the newly created chain to the clothing.
First, select the 3D chain to be applied in the 3D window.
Then press the application button on the right side of the new chain in the object window.
You can apply it.
If you first select a chain, then click the application button in the upper right corner of the object window,
a new default chain will be created at the bottom.
And it will be applied directly to the selected 3D chain.
The copy will copy a similar one with a chain pattern.
Select a chain in the object window.
In the attribute editor at the bottom,
you can modify the overall shape of the chain.
Including the basic information of the chain, the type of the chain, and the size of the chain.
You can see the changes.
The corresponding chain in the 3D window will also change.
While maintaining the overall shape,
you can also select the details of various components such as the editor, the head, and the chain.
When you use the option to press and hold the head, the chain, or the stop component,
it will immediately select the entire chain component.
At this time, if you press and hold the button again to edit the object,
it will only select a specific object.
If the selected object is divided into two or more grid,
then press and hold the button again to select only a specific object.
Here, click the chain part again to edit the size of the chain separately.
After the modification, the chain component will be selected again.
You can press and hold the button again to edit a certain material color separately.
You can also unify the modification.
You can also select the chain and cloth to modify the material color, etc.
It is the same as the previous operation.
You can also save the design chain pattern as a GPS format,
and use it for other projects.
In the object window, select the chain to be saved.
Click the save button at the top of the property editor to save the file.
The saved ZPS chain file can be opened and opened by the button next to it at any time,
and re-loaded in other projects.
Here, open another clothing project file.
In the object window, select the chain,
find the open icon in the property editor,
and select the ZPS file to be saved.
You can see the new sample in the chain selection card list,
and it is also applied to the 3D clothing chain.
In addition,
you can press and hold the right button on the unused chain in the object window,
and you can rename, delete, and reset it.
It is an effective way to clean up the list by deleting all unused chains.
You can see the new sample in the object window,
and it is also applied to the 3D clothing chain.